{
    "nivel": "Sumas y Restas",
    "secciones": [
      {
        "seccion": "Suma simple",
        "etapas": [
          { "etapa": 1, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "1 + 1",
                "respuesta": 2,
                "opciones": [0, 2, 3, 1]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 + 5",
                "respuesta": 6,
                "opciones": [7, 6, 5, 8]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 + 9",
                "respuesta": 10,
                "opciones": [10, 12, 8, 7]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "3 + 2",
                "respuesta": 5,
                "opciones": [1, 3, 4, 5]
              }   
          ] },
          { "etapa": 2, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "1 + 4",
                "respuesta": 2,
                "opciones": [6, 2, 3, 5]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "3 + 3",
                "respuesta": 6,
                "opciones": [5, 2, 6, 7]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 + 7",
                "respuesta": 8,
                "opciones": [8, 6, 5, 7]
              }
          ] },
          { "etapa": 3, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "4 + 4",
                "respuesta": 8,
                "opciones": [0, 8, 3, 1]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "6 + 2",
                "respuesta": 8,
                "opciones": [9, 8, 5, 7]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "4 + 3",
                "respuesta": 7,
                "opciones": [7, 6, 2, 5]
              }
          ] },
          { "etapa": 4, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "10 + 1",
                "respuesta": 11,
                "opciones": [10, 13, 11, 12]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "8 + 8",
                "respuesta": 16,
                "opciones": [16, 17, 15, 17]
              }
          ] }
        ]
      },
      {
        "seccion": "Restas",
        "etapas": [
            { "etapa": 1, "preguntas": [ 
                {
                    "pregunta": "4 - 4",
                    "respuesta": 0,
                    "opciones": [0, 8, 3, 1]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "6 + 2",
                    "respuesta": 4,
                    "opciones": [4, 3, 8, 7]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "4 - 3",
                    "respuesta": 1,
                    "opciones": [7, 6, 1, 5]
                  }
              ] },
              { "etapa": 2, "preguntas": [ 
                {
                    "pregunta": "10 - 1",
                    "respuesta": 11,
                    "opciones": [10, 9, 11, 8]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "8 - 8",
                    "respuesta": 0,
                    "opciones": [1, 16, 0, 15]
                  }
              ] }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }